A Guide to the Trilateral Commission (North America) records FA420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Task Force Reports/Projects, 1973-2001; 2; 44.99 Cubic Feet 115 letter document boxes and 1 record storage box
  - Report #23: The Trilateral Countries in the International Economy of the 1980s, 1982
    - New Vistas Task Force - Laursen Drafts, 1980-1981 (Box 144, Folder 1571)
    - New Vistas Task Force - First Draft and Cover Material for Consultants Meetings, 1980 November (Box 144, Folder 1572)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Drafts (Box 144, Folder 1573)
    - New Vistas Task Force, 1979-1981 (Box 144, Folder 1574)
    - New Vistas Task Force - North American Consultants Meetings, New York, 1990 November 18 (Box 144, Folder 1575)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Authors - Background Material, 1979-1980 (Box 144, Folder 1576)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Galleys (Box 145, Folder 1577)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Hirono Last Draft, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 1578)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Final Camps Draft, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 1579)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Authors Meeting, New York, 1981 October 5 (Box 145, Folder 1580)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Final Laursen Draft, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 1581)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Front Matter (Box 145, Folder 1582)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Galley Proofs - Hirono Article (Box 145, Folder 1583)
    - Johns Hopkins University Press, 1979 (Box 145, Folder 1584)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Meeting, Discussion Draft, 1981 October 5 (Box 146, Folder 1585)
    - New Vistas Task Force - N.A. Consultants Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1980 November 13 (Box 146, Folder 1586)
    - New Vistas Task Force - George S. Franklin Desk File, 1980 (Box 146, Folder 1587)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Draft, 1981 October 22 (Box 146, Folder 1588)
    - New Vistas Task Force - George S. Franklin Desk File (Box 146, Folder 1589)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Post Publication Correspondence, 1982 (Box 146, Folder 1590)
    - New Vistas Task Force - Camps, Hirono, Laursen Correspondence, 1980 (Box 146, Folder 1591)
    - Second Combined Volume - Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 146, Folder 1592)
    - Second Combined Volume - Triangle Papers 9-14 (Box 146, Folder 1593)
    - Second Combined Volume - Dummy (Box 146, Folder 1594)
    - Third Combined Volume - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 146, Folder 1595)
    - Third Combined Volume - Foreword, Authors and Jacket Cover, 1981 (Box 146, Folder 1596)
    - Third Combined Volume - First Dummy, 1980 (Box 146, Folder 1597)
  - Report #24: East-West Trade at a Crossroads: Economic Relations with the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe, 1982
    - East West Trade Task Force - Roosa's Possible Meeting with Senators and Congressmen - Hosted by Foley (Box 147, Folder 1598)
    - East West Trade Task Force - U.S.-Soviet Relations (Box 147, Folder 1599)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Meeting, Cosmos Club, 1981 September 26-27 (Box 147, Folder 1599A)
    - East West Trade Task Force - East West Trade at the Crossroads (Box 147, Folder 1600)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Hard Copies of Report Sent To, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 1601)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Responses to East-West Mailing, 1982 October (Box 147, Folder 1602)
    - East West Trade Task Force - East West Trade Press Conference, Toronto, 1982 September 8 (Box 147, Folder 1603)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Mailing of Draft To Press, 1982 June (Box 147, Folder 1604)
    - East West Trade Task Force, 1982 (Box 147, Folder 1604A)
    - East West Trade Task Force - First Authors Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1981 September 26-27 (Box 147, Folder 1605)
    - East West Trade Task Force - General (Box 148, Folder 1606)
    - East West Trade Task Force - General (Box 148, Folder 1606A)
    - East West Trade Task Force - General (Box 148, Folder 1606B)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Drafts (Box 148, Folder 1606C)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Drafts (Box 148, Folder 1606)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Drafts - Matsukawa First Draft, 1982 January (Box 149, Folder 1607)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Post Publication Correspondence (Box 149, Folder 1608)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Publication Info and Correspondence (Box 149, Folder 1609)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Draft Prep and Pre-Plenary Correspondence (Box 149, Folder 1610)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Post Tokyo Correspondence (Box 149, Folder 1611)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Drafts - Roosa Reichart Draft, 1982 January (Box 149, Folder 1612)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Drafts - Roosa Draft of Chapter 3, 1982 January (Box 149, Folder 1613)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Authors Meeting, New York, 1981 February 5-7 (Box 149, Folder 1614)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Drafts - Gutowski Draft, 1981 October; 1982 February (Box 149, Folder 1615)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Drafts, 1982 January 28 (Box 149, Folder 1616)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Drafts - First Roosa Draft (December 1981) with Papers of John Hardt, 1981 December (Box 149, Folder 1617)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Preliminary Correspondence (Box 150, Folder 1618)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Clippings (Box 150, Folder 1619)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Discussion and Articles from the Berlin Meeting, 1981 October (Box 150, Folder 1620)
    - East West Trade Task Force - Drafts - Tokyo Draft, 1982 April (Box 150, Folder 1621)
  - Report #25: Sharing International Responsibilities Among the Trilateral Countries, 1982
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 150, Folder 1622)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Preliminary Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 150, Folder 1623)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Drafts - Revised Drafts, after January and before February 22, 1982 (Box 150, Folder 1624)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Meeting, 1982 February 22-23 (Box 150, Folder 1625)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - First Authors Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1981 March 28 (Box 150, Folder 1626)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Authors Meeting, 1981 January 25-26 (Box 150, Folder 1627)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Second Authors Meeting, New York, 1981 June 21-23 (Box 150, Folder 1628)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Drafts - Tokyo, 1982 March (Box 150, Folder 1629)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - CBH Chapter II (Box 150, Folder 1630)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Drafts - Ushiba (Box 151, Folder 1631)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Drafts - Allison (Box 151, Folder 1632)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - General (Box 151, Folder 1633)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - General (Box 151, Folder 1633A)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - General (Box 151, Folder 1633B)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - General (Box 151, Folder 1633C)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Regional Chapter (Box 151, Folder 1634)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Concluding Chapter (Box 151, Folder 1635)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Intro and Conceptual Chapter (Box 152, Folder 1636)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Post Publication Correspondence, 1983 (Box 152, Folder 1637)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Publication Info, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 1638)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Post Tokyo Correspondence, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 1639)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Draft Preparation and Pre-Plenary Correspondence, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 1640)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 1641)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 1641A)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 1641B)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Conclusion (Box 152, Folder 1642)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Canada Section, 1982 October 7 (Box 152, Folder 1643)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Meetings, 1982 (Box 152, Folder 1644)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Drafts - Allison (Box 153, Folder 1645)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Drafts - de Montbrial (Box 153, Folder 1646)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Canada Section, 1982 (Box 153, Folder 1647)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - General Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 153, Folder 1648)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 153, Folder 1649)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Mailing, 1983 (Box 153, Folder 1650)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Drafts - Ushiba (Box 153, Folder 1651)
    - Sharing Responsibilities Task Force - Allison's Possible Meeting with Congressmen and Senators - Hosted by Roth, 1982 (Box 153, Folder 1652)
  - Report #26: Trilateral Security: Defense and Arms Control Policies in the 1980s, 1983
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Discussion Drafts, 1983 March (Box 153, Folder 1653)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Gerard Smith - Press Event, 1983 September (Box 153, Folder 1654)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Budget, 1983 (Box 153, Folder 1655)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force, 1982 (Box 153, Folder 1656)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Drafts - Europe, 1982-1983 (Box 153, Folder 1657)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Drafts - Japan, 1982-1983 (Box 153, Folder 1658)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 153, Folder 1659)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 154, Folder 1660)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Discussion of Report, Rome, 1960 October 29 (Box 154, Folder 1661)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Drafts (Box 154, Folder 1662)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Drafts (Box 154, Folder 1663)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Drafts (Box 154, Folder 1664)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Distribution of Report, 1983 (Box 154, Folder 1665)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Distribution of Report, 1983 October 11 (Box 154, Folder 1666)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - N.A. Consultants Meeting, 1982 June 23 (Box 155, Folder 1667)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Preliminary Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 155, Folder 1668)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Press Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 October 7 (Box 155, Folder 1669)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Front Matter (Box 155, Folder 1670)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - N.A. Consultation Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 February 1 (Box 155, Folder 1671)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Authors Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 November 18 (Box 155, Folder 1672)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Drafts - Smith-Makins First Draft, 1982 September 1 (Box 155, Folder 1673)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Drafts - Smith-Makins Draft Outline, 1981 January 28 (Box 155, Folder 1674)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Clippings, 1981 (Box 155, Folder 1675)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Drafts - Final, 1983 April (Box 155, Folder 1676)
    - Trilateral Security Task Force - Drafts - Final, 1983 April (Box 155, Folder 1676A)
  - Report #27: Facilitating Development in a Changing Third World: Trade, Finance, Aid, 1983
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - Publication, 1983 (Box 155, Folder 1677)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - Preliminary Correspondence, 1982 (Box 155, Folder 1678)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - Isaiah Frank Paper, 1982 December (Box 156, Folder 1679)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - Authors Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1982 November19 (Box 156, Folder 1680)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - Authors Meeting, New York, 1982 September 11 (Box 156, Folder 1681)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - Front Matter (Box 156, Folder 1682)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force, 1983 (Box 156, Folder 1683)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - GSF Desk File (Box 156, Folder 1684)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - Distribution of Report, 1983 (Box 156, Folder 1685)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - General (Box 157, Folder 1685A)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - General (Box 157, Folder 1685B)
    - Strategies for Assistance to Developing Countries Task Force - General (Box 157, Folder 1685C)
  - Report #28: Democracy Must Work: A Trilateral Agenda for the Decade, 1984
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Authors Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 December 1-2 (Box 158, Folder 1686)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Authors Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 December 1-2 (Box 158, Folder 1687)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Preliminary Correspondence - Owen, Brzezinski, Okita (Box 158, Folder 1688)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Publication, 1984 (Box 158, Folder 1689)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Discussion Draft, 1984 February (Box 158, Folder 1690)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Okita - "Economic Response" (Box 158, Folder 1691)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Stewart - Background Paper, 1983 (Box 158, Folder 1692)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force, 1983 (Box 159, Folder 1693)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force, 1984 (Box 159, Folder 1693A)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Owen/Stewart - "Social Response" (Box 159, Folder 1694)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Brzezinski - "Political Responses" (Box 159, Folder 1695)
    - Democracy Must Work Task Force - Schedule (Box 159, Folder 1696)
  - Report #29: Agricultural Policy and Trade: Adjusting Domestic Programs in an International Framework, 1985
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Preliminary Correspondence, 1983 (Box 160, Folder 1697)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Front Matter (Box 160, Folder 1698)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Front Matter (Box 160, Folder 1699)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Post Plenary Changes and Preparation of Final Draft (Box 160, Folder 1700)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - U.S. Appendix for Publication (Box 160, Folder 1701)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force, 1986 (Box 160, Folder 1702)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Correspondence, etc., 1984-1986 (Box 160, Folder 1703)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Authors Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1985 February 4-5 (Box 160, Folder 1704)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - First Authors Meeting, 1984 September 9-10 (Box 160, Folder 1705)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Discussion of First Draft, Washington, D.C., 1984 December 4 (Box 161, Folder 1706)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Initial Writings, 1984 January (Box 161, Folder 1707)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Johnson - Initial Paper on U.S., 1984 August 1 (Box 161, Folder 1708)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Johnson - First Draft, 1984 November (Box 161, Folder 1709)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Johnson - Second Draft, 1985 January (Box 161, Folder 1710)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Johnson - Third Draft, 1985 March (Box 161, Folder 1711)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Introduction, 1985 January (Box 161, Folder 1712)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Chapter 9 (Box 161, Folder 1713)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Heck Editing of Johnson Third Draft (Box 161, Folder 1714)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Hemmi, Europe and Warley Changes in Draft for Tokyo Plenary (and Johnson reaction) (Box 161, Folder 1715)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Draft - Tokyo Plenary (Box 162, Folder 1716)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Johnson - Post Plenary Changes (Box 162, Folder 1717)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Heck Editing of Main Text After Plenary (Box 162, Folder 1718)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 162, Folder 1719)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Submissions from Europe (Box 162, Folder 1720)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Europe Appendix for Publication (Box 162, Folder 1721)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Submissions from Japan (Box 162, Folder 1722)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Japan Appendix for Publication (Box 162, Folder 1723)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Warley Paper on Canada (first and final version) (Box 162, Folder 1724)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Other Appendix Material (Box 162, Folder 1725)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Background Papers (Box 162, Folder 1726)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Background Papers - Warley, Pearce, Tangermann (Box 163, Folder 1727)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Tables (Box 163, Folder 1728)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Tables (Box 163, Folder 1729)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Other Appendix Tables (Box 163, Folder 1730)
    - Agricultural Policy and Trade Task Force - Tables in Main Text (Box 163, Folder 1731)
  - Report #30: East Asian Security and the Trilateral Countries, 1985
    - East Asian Security Task Force - Correspondence, etc., 1985 (Box 163, Folder 1732)
    - East Asian Security Task Force - Draft Report, 1985 (Box 163, Folder 1733)
  - Report #31: Prospects for East-West Relations, 1986
    - East-West Relations Task Force, 1985-1986 (Box 163, Folder 1734)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Drafts - Editing of Hyland Third Draft (Box 163, Folder 1735)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Drafts - Madrid (Box 164, Folder 1736)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Drafts - Editing of Third Draft (Box 164, Folder 1737)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Background Material (Box 164, Folder 1738)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Front Matter (Box 164, Folder 1739)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Drafts - Hyland First Draft, 1985 November 1 (Box 164, Folder 1740)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Drafts - Hyland Second Draft, 1986 January (Box 164, Folder 1741)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Drafts - Hyland Third Draft (Box 164, Folder 1742)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Drafts - Initial Draft Writings (Box 164, Folder 1743)
    - East-West Relations Task Force - Authors Meetings, Summaries, New York, 1985 August; November; December (Box 164, Folder 1744)
  - Report #32: Conditions for Partnership in International Economic Management, 1986
    - Partnership Task Force - Main Files, Drafts (Box 165, Folder 1745)
    - Partnership Task Force - Excerpts of Published Reports Prepared in July Press Event, 1986 (Box 165, Folder 1746)
    - Partnership Task Force - Drafts - Madrid Plenary (Box 165, Folder 1747)
    - Partnership Task Force - Front Matter (Box 165, Folder 1748)
    - Partnership Task Force - Bergsten - U.S. Essay (Box 165, Folder 1749)
    - Partnership Task Force - Miyazaki - Japan Essay (Box 165, Folder 1750)
    - Partnership Task Force - Davignon - Europe Essay (Box 165, Folder 1751)
    - Partnership Task Force - Lawson - Canada Essay (Box 165, Folder 1752)
    - Partnership Task Force - Intro and Conclusion Drafts I (Box 165, Folder 1753)
    - Partnership Task Force - Intro and Conclusion Drafts II (Box 166, Folder 1754)
    - Partnership Task Force - Meetings, Pre-Draft Document (Box 166, Folder 1755)
    - Partnership Task Force - Cover and General Printing (Box 166, Folder 1756)
    - Partnership Task Force - Background (Box 166, Folder 1757)
    - Partnership Task Force, 1984-1986 (Box 166, Folder 1758)
    - Partnership Task Force - Correspondence, Telexes, etc. (Box 166, Folder 1759)
  - Report #33: Restoring Growth in the Debt-Laden Third World, 1987
    - Third World Task Force - U.S. Treasury File - Background Materials, 1985 (Box 166, Folder 1760)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Congressional Summit Material, 1986 December (Box 166, Folder 1761)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Narusawa Pieces (Box 166, Folder 1762)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts - de Carmoy First and Second Draft, 1986 (Box 167, Folder 1763)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts - de Carmoy Draft, 1986 December (Box 167, Folder 1764)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts - de Carmoy Draft, 1987 January (Box 167, Folder 1765)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts - Krugman Draft, 1987 January (Box 167, Folder 1766)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts - Krugman Draft, 1987 February (Box 167, Folder 1767)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Discussion Draft, 1987 February (Box 168, Folder 1767A)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts - Revised Draft (Post San Francisco Draft from Cambridge), 1987 April (Box 168, Folder 1768)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts - Narusawa Revised Draft, 1987 April (Box 168, Folder 1769)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Broad Chapter IV - Aborted (Box 168, Folder 1770)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Overall Version Sent to Cambridge, 1953 December 18 (Box 168, Folder 1771)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Overall Version Sent to Cambridge, 1987 August 20 (Box 168, Folder 1772)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Intro (Box 169, Folder 1773)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Chapter I (Box 169, Folder 1774)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Chapter II (Box 169, Folder 1775)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Chapter III (Box 169, Folder 1776)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Chapter IV (Box 169, Folder 1777)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Chapter V (Box 169, Folder 1778)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Chapter VI (Box 169, Folder 1779)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Chapter VII (Box 169, Folder 1780)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Appendix (Box 169, Folder 1781)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Front Matter (Box 169, Folder 1782)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Tables and Figures (Box 169, Folder 1783)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - de Carmoy Separate Essay (Box 169, Folder 1784)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Biographies (Box 169, Folder 1785)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts (Box 170, Folder 1786)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - General, 1987 (Box 170, Folder 1787)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - References (Box 170, Folder 1788)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Chronology Debt Crisis (Box 170, Folder 1789)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts - Narusawa Draft, 1987 January-April (Box 170, Folder 1790)
    - Third World Debt Task Force - Drafts - Discussion Draft, 1987 February (Box 170, Folder 1791)
  - Report #34: Science and Technology in Trilateral Relations: Competition and Cooperation (Draft), 1988
    - Technology Project - Drafts - Discussion Drafts, San Francisco., 1987 March (Box 170, Folder 1792)
    - Technology Project - Drafts - Brown and Branscomb Changes in San Francisco Draft (Box 170, Folder 1793)
    - Technology Project - Drafts - Brown and Branscomb Changes in San Francisco Draft - Heck Adjustments, 1989 September (Box 170, Folder 1794)
    - Technology Project - Initial Writings and Outlines (Box 170, Folder 1795)
    - Technology Project - Drafts - San Francisco Draft, 1987 March (Box 171, Folder 1796)
    - Technology Project - European Submission, 1988 February (Box 171, Folder 1797)
    - Technology Project - Correspondence, Telexes, Notes, etc., 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 1798)